const BANK = [
    { "question": "You probably know of Mario in the 'Super Mario Bros.' games, but what is the name of Mario's taller brother who normally wears green?",
        "optionone": 'Luigi',
        "optiontwo": 'Goomba',
        "optionthree": 'Toad',
        "optionfour": 'Howard',
        "correctAnswer": 'Luigi'
    },

    { "question": "What is the name of Mario's hungry green dinosaur friend that Mario may ride around on?",
    "optionone": 'R.O.B.',
    "optiontwo": 'Kamek',
    "optionthree": 'Peach',
    "optionfour": 'Yoshi',
    "correctAnswer": 'Yoshi'
    },

    {"question": "What is the name of the main villain that Mario must rescue the Mushroom Kingdom from?",
    "optionone": 'Peach',
    "optiontwo": 'Bowser',
    "optionthree": 'Geno',
    "optionfour": 'Daisy',
    "correctAnswer": 'Bowser'},

    {"question": "What is the name of the always green clad hero in the 'Legend of Zelda' Series?",
    "optionone": 'Meta Knight',
    "optiontwo": 'Impa',
    "optionthree": 'Link',
    "optionfour": 'Yoshi',
    "correctAnswer": 'Link'},

    {"question": "What is the name of the bounty hunter from the Metroid Series?",
    "optionone": 'Samus Aran',
    "optiontwo": 'Roy',
    "optionthree": 'Marth',
    "optionfour": 'Lucina',
    "correctAnswer": 'Samus Aran'},

    {"question": "What is the name of the pink puffy hero that inhales his enemies like a vacuum?",
        "optionone": 'Malo',
        "optiontwo": 'Wario',
        "optionthree": 'Kirby',
        "optionfour": 'Ryu',
        "correctAnswer": 'Kirby'},

    {"question": "What is the name of the diminutive boxer you play as from the 'Punch Out' series?",
        "optionone": 'E Honda',
        "optiontwo": 'Little Mac',
        "optionthree": 'Glass Joe',
        "optionfour": 'King Hippo',
        "correctAnswer": 'Little Mac'},
                    
    { "question": "What is the name of Mario's larger yellow clad doppleganger rival that has an affinity for garlic?",
    "optionone": 'Cloud',
    "optiontwo": 'Daisy',
    "optionthree": 'Toad',
    "optionfour": 'Wario',
    "correctAnswer": 'Wario'},
    
    { "question": "What is the name of the physical robot that was originally included with the Nintendo Entertainment System?",
        "optionone": 'Sonic',
        "optiontwo": 'Pit',
        "optionthree": 'R.O.B.',
        "optionfour": 'Ken',
        "correctAnswer": 'R.O.B.'},
                        
    {"question": "Which of these names is not a pokemon?",
        "optionone": 'Axolotl',
        "optiontwo": 'Bulbasaur',
        "optionthree": 'Charmander',
        "optionfour": 'Dartrix',
        "correctAnswer": 'Axolotl'}];
